[
    {
        "Question": "occasionally",
        "Answer": "once in a while",
        "Options": "sometimes"
    },
    {
        "Question": "convinced",
        "Answer": "persuaded",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cardinal",
        "Answer": "fundamental",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pertinent",
        "Answer": "relevant",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "revered",
        "Answer": "honored",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "generated",
        "Answer": "produced",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "entail",
        "Answer": "involve",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prospect",
        "Answer": "possibility",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "quantifiable",
        "Answer": "measurable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "heightened",
        "Answer": "increased",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accounts for",
        "Answer": "explains",
        "Options": "describe"
    },
    {
        "Question": "appearance",
        "Answer": "arrival/ rise",
        "Options": "shown up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "evolve",
        "Answer": "developed",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "widespread",
        "Answer": "common",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "envision",
        "Answer": "imagine",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "desiccated",
        "Answer": "dry",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "excrete",
        "Answer": "expel",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obsession with",
        "Answer": "fixation on",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "distort",
        "Answer": "misinterpret",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "vicinity",
        "Answer": "region",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "being a drain on the tree",
        "Answer": "wasting the treeâ€™s resources",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "myriad",
        "Answer": "many",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ample",
        "Answer": "plenty",
        "Options": "spacious"
    },
    {
        "Question": "observation",
        "Answer": "finding",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "admiration for",
        "Answer": "high opinion of",
        "Options": "respect"
    },
    {
        "Question": "plunge",
        "Answer": "drop",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "earn",
        "Answer": "acquire",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "surpluses",
        "Answer": "extra goods",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "urged",
        "Answer": "encouraged",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "propose",
        "Answer": "offer the theory",
        "Options": "suggest"
    },
    {
        "Question": "discernible",
        "Answer": "noticeable",
        "Options": "discriminating"
    },
    {
        "Question": "signifying",
        "Answer": "indicating",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hastened",
        "Answer": "rushed",
        "Options": "accelerated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "underexpertedly",
        "Answer": "surprisingly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sufficient",
        "Answer": "enough",
        "Options": "adequate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "harsh",
        "Answer": "severe",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "vital",
        "Answer": "essential",
        "Options": "unprotected"
    },
    {
        "Question": "enjoy",
        "Answer": "experience",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ever-shifting",
        "Answer": "constant changing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obviously",
        "Answer": "clearly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ensure",
        "Answer": "guarantee",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "static",
        "Answer": "unchanging",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "optimize",
        "Answer": "make the best use of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detect",
        "Answer": "find",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "intervals",
        "Answer": "periods",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "admirably",
        "Answer": "very well",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "engraved",
        "Answer": "carved",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "irreversible",
        "Answer": "permanent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "ambitious",
        "Answer": "impressive but difficult to achieve",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "had priority",
        "Answer": "had advantages",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "evaluate",
        "Answer": "judge",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "deflect",
        "Answer": "redirect",
        "Options": "turn from its direction of movement"
    },
    {
        "Question": "authoritative",
        "Answer": "official",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "vessel",
        "Answer": "craft",
        "Options": "able to survive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "depicts",
        "Answer": "portrays",
        "Options": "pictured"
    },
    {
        "Question": "correlate",
        "Answer": "match ",
        "Options": "accord with"
    },
    {
        "Question": "plague",
        "Answer": "cause trouble for",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "prestige",
        "Answer": "status",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "no wonder",
        "Answer": "unsurprising",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "converge",
        "Answer": "come together",
        "Options": "move closer"
    },
    {
        "Question": "inaccessible",
        "Answer": "unreachable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "distribution",
        "Answer": "geographic range",
        "Options": "dispersion"
    },
    {
        "Question": "extant",
        "Answer": "remaining",
        "Options": "existing"
    },
    {
        "Question": "faithful",
        "Answer": "exact",
        "Options": "accurate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "besides",
        "Answer": "in addition to",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "hints",
        "Answer": "clues",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "authenticity",
        "Answer": "genineness",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "proliferation",
        "Answer": "growth",
        "Options": "increase"
    },
    {
        "Question": "encounters",
        "Answer": "meets",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impeded",
        "Answer": "restricted",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "diligent",
        "Answer": "careful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "tremendous",
        "Answer": "enormous",
        "Options": "huge"
    },
    {
        "Question": "distinction",
        "Answer": "difference",
        "Options": "excellence"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compacted",
        "Answer": "compressed",
        "Options": "concise"
    },
    {
        "Question": "compatible",
        "Answer": "equivalent",
        "Options": "consistent"
    },
    {
        "Question": "tactic",
        "Answer": "strategy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "allusion",
        "Answer": "reference",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consumption",
        "Answer": "utilization",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sequentially",
        "Answer": "one after another",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "unpromising",
        "Answer": "unfavorable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "humble",
        "Answer": "modest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "appreciation",
        "Answer": "recognition",
        "Options": "noticeable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "abound",
        "Answer": "are numerous",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "allowing",
        "Answer": "enabling",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "devastate",
        "Answer": "destroy/ ruin",
        "Options": "extremely destructive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "conclusive",
        "Answer": "final",
        "Options": "ultimate"
    },
    {
        "Question": "advent",
        "Answer": "arrival",
        "Options": "beginning"
    },
    {
        "Question": "innovation",
        "Answer": "new development",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "focus",
        "Answer": "concentrate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "infrequent",
        "Answer": "uncommon",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enduring",
        "Answer": "lasting",
        "Options": "withstanding"
    },
    {
        "Question": "lasted",
        "Answer": "endured",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mechanism for",
        "Answer": "means of",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "elite",
        "Answer": "excellent person",
        "Options": "upper class"
    },
    {
        "Question": "respectively",
        "Answer": "separately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "obliged",
        "Answer": "required",
        "Options": "responsible"
    },
    {
        "Question": "yield",
        "Answer": "produce",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "superseded",
        "Answer": "replaced",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "persuasively",
        "Answer": "convincingly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "spheres",
        "Answer": "areas",
        "Options": ""
    }
]